Guide to the Steele Ranch Records, 1855-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES A. CORRESPONDENCE: 1855-1973
  - Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 35. 1924, Oct. 24.Houston, Texas. Southern Pacific Lines (E.J.P.) to Southern Pacific Employees., T.L.
    - 36. 1925, July 10.S.F., Ca. P.E. Springer to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1926, April 6.S.F., Ca. _____(?) (Bohemian Club) to _____(?)., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1926, May 8.N.P. C.F. Humphrey to Smith-Linden & Co., T.L.
    - 39. 1926, Oct. 14.S.F., Ca. Enterprise Electric Works (J.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1926, Oct. 18.S.F., Ca. Mercantile Trust Co. of Calif. (A.M.F.) to C.R.S., T.L.
    - 41. 1926, Nov. 22.Pescadero, Ca. C.F. Humphrey to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1927, Feb. 10.S.F., Ca. C.F.H.* to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 43. 1927, Feb. 10.N.P. C.F.H.* to E.W. Clark., T.L.
    - 44. 1927, Dec. 7.S.F., Ca. C.F.H.* to W.[F.S.] re: ranching and crops., A.L.S.
    - 45. 1928, Feb. 2.N.P. W.C. to Mercantile Trust Co., T.L.
    - 46. 1928, Feb. 20.S.F., Ca. American Trust Co. to C.R.S., T.L.S.
    - 47. 1928, Nov. 2.San Jose, Ca. Farmers Service Co. (R.H.H.*) to W.F.S. re: finances., T.L.S.
    - 48. 1928, Dec. 19.S.F., Ca. R.E.S. to Catherine [C.B.S.], A.L.S.
    - 49. 1929, May 16.N.P. C.F.H.* to Bank of Italy., T.L.S.
    - 50. 1929, May 23.Pescadero, Ca. C.F.H.* to W.F.S. re: ranch finances., T.L.
    - 51. 1929, May 31.S.F., Ca. C.F.H.* to W.S.S. re: ranch finances., T.L.S.
    - 52. 1929, Aug. 20.San Jose, Ca. W.S. Stephenson to Walter H. Moore, Constable., T.L.S.
      (bad water damage on this letter).
    - 53. 1929, Aug. 20.San Jose, Ca. W.S. Stephenson to Edward I. McAullay (?)., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1929, Aug. 20.Vancouver, B.C. Office of Game Commission (A.B.W.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1929, Sept. 24.S.F., Ca. C.F.H.* to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 56. 1929, Oct. 4.S.F., Ca. C.F.H.* to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 57. 1929, Oct. 21.S.F., Ca. C.F.H.* to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 58. 1929, Nov. 27.Same as # 57.
    - 59. 1929, Dec. 21.Portland, Oregon. Howard to C.F.H.*, T.L.
  - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1. 1930, Jan. 3.S.F., Ca. C.F.H.* to W.F.S., T.L.S.
      (badly damaged - some words obliterated).
    - 2. 1930, Mar. 10.Pescadero, Ca. C.F.H.* to Pacific Daily Review., T.L.
    - 3. 1930, April 25.Pescadero, Ca. C.F.H.* to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1930, June 22.S.F., Ca. Stella R. Hailstone to W.F.S. re: ranch - legal matters., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1930, July 18.S.F., Ca. C.F.H.* to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1930, Aug. 18.S.F., Ca. Star Drilling Machine Co. (N.W.G.) to W.F.S. re: ranch machinery., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1930, Nov. 3.S.F., Ca. U.S. Coast Guard, Calif. Division (E.B.*) to C.F.H.), T.L.
    - 8. 1930, Nov. 6.S.F., Ca. Calif. Desert Products Co. (L.R.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1930, Nov. 10.S.F., Ca. Same as # 8.
    - 10. 1930, Nov. 14.Redwood Manufacturers Co. (H.B.W.) to W.F.S. re: redwood pipes., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1930, Nov. 15.Pescadero, Ca. C.F.H.* to Eugene Blake Jr.. Captain U.S. Coast Guard., T.L.
    - 12. 1930, Nov. 21.S.F., Ca. Pelton Water Wheel Co. (C.M.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1930, Nov. 26.S.F., Ca. Calif. Desert Products Co. (L.R.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1930, Dec. 2.S.F., Ca. R.E.S. to Will [W.F.S.], A.L.S.
    - 15. 1930, Dec. 3.Redwood City, Ca. Ross & Ross to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1930, Dec. 11.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1930, Dec. 13.S.F., Ca. Redwood Manufacturers Co. (G.W.N.) to W.F.S. re: irrigation - pipe line project from Waddell Creek., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1. 1931, Jan. 8.S.F., Ca. Western Pipe & Steel Co. (A.C.P.) to W.H.S. [W.F.S.], T.L.S.
    - 2. 1931, Jan. 9.S.F., Ca. Columbia Casualty Co. (A.J.L.*) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1931, Jan. 13.Milbrae, Ca. Milbrae Dairy (R.E.S.) to W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1931, Jan. 13.S.F., Ca. Calif. Desert Products Co. (L.R.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1931, Feb. 16.Cleveland, Ohio. Carnegie Steel Co. (W.H.B.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1931, Feb. 20.S.F., Ca. Columbia Steel. Co. (T.W.B.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1931, Mar 13.S.F., Ca. Pacific Pipe Co. (E.I.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1931, Mar. 27.Santa Cruz, Ca. Rittenhouse & Snyder. (E.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1931, April 1.Los Angeles, Ca. A.O. Smith Corp. (H.A.B.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1931, April 3.Stanford Univ., Ca. Theodore J. Hoover to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1931, April 13.Los Angeles, Ca. A.O. Smith Corp. (H.A.B.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1931, April 13.San Mateo, Ca. Kirkbride, Wilson & Brooks (E.A.W.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1931, April 15.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co. (G.S.*) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1931, April 21.West Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Corrugated Culvert Co. (E.W.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1931, April 22.Green Oaks, Pescadero, Ca. Unknown to Colonel & Mrs. Fitch., T.L.
    - 16. 1931, April 23.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1931, April 27.S.F., Ca. Railroad Commission of the State of Calif. (H.G.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1931, April 29.Los Angeles, Ca. Robertson & Co. (J.M.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1931, April 29.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1931, May 1.N.P. [Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca.]. Unknown [W.F.S.] to Railroad Commission of the State of Calif., T.L.
    - 21. 1931, May 1.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to W.F.S. re: Hoover-Steele agreement., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1931, May 3.Green Oaks Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin re: Hoover-Steele agreement., T.L.
    - 23. 1931, May 4.Los Angeles, Ca. E.D. Taylor Co. (E.C.K.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1931, May 4.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1931, May 6.S.F., Ca. Ajax Construction Co. (F.A.D.) to W.F.S. re: water pumping plant., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1931, May 6.L.A., Ca. Wilson Pipe Co. (J.J.W.*) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1931, May 7.L.A., Ca. Standard Pipe & Supply Co. (J.F.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1931, May 8.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin re: right-of-way for pipe line., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1931, May 8.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to David Atkins., T.L.S.
    - 30. Same as # 29.
    - 31. 1931, May 8.N.P. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to David Atkins., T.L.
    - 32. 1931, May 8.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1931, May 13.Los Angeles, Ca. Wilson-Spear Co. (A.W.S.*) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1931, May 13.Sunnyvale, Ca. Calif. Concrete Products Co., Inc. (J.T.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1931, May 13.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to Arthur M. Brandt., T.L.
    - 36. 1931, May 13.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1931, May 18.Houston, Texas. Mother to W.F.S. re: gas line pipe., tel.
    - 38. 1931, May 18.S.F., Ca. Pelton Water Wheel Co. (C.M.K.) to W.F.S.re: irrigation system and pumping plant., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1931, May 19.L. A., Ca. E.D. Taylor Co. (E.D.T.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1931, May 20.L.A., Ca. Wilson Pipe Co. (J.J.W.*) to R.E.Steele., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1931, May 20.Redwood City, Ca. Ross & Ross to W.F.S. re: pipe line right-of-way., T.L.S.
    - 42. Same as #41 except letter is not signed.
    - 43. 1931, May 22.L.A., Ca. Wilson-Spear Co. (A.W.S.*) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1931, May 22.S.F., Ca. Western Pipe & Steel Co. (A.C.P.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1931, May 22.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1931, May 25.L.A., Ca. E.D.Taylor Co. (E.D.T.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 47. 1931, May 25.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to E.D.Rogers., T.L.S.
    - 48. Same as # 47 except letter is not signed.
    - 49. 1931, May 26.L.A., Ca. E.D. Taylor Co. (E.D.T.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 50. 1931, May 26.San Jose, Ca. Standard Oil Co. of Ca. (J.C.W.) to A.E. DeVoto., T.L.S.
    - 51. 1931, May 26.Santa Cruz, Ca. Walter (?) Camron (?) to W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 52. 1931. May 27.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to E.D. Rodgers., T.L.S.
    - 53. 1931, June 3.L.A., Ca. Standard Pipe & Supply Co. (J.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1931, June 3.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1931, June 4.Oakland, Ca. Contractors Machinery Exchange (J.J.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 56. 1931, June 6.S.F., Ca. Railroad Commission of the State of Calif. (H.G.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 57. 1931, June 9.L.A, Ca. Standard Pipe & Supply Co. (J.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 58. 1931, June 13.West Berkeley. Ca. Calif. Corrugated Culvert Co. (E.W.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 59. 1931, June 13.West Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Corrugated Culvert Co. (E.W.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S. (copy).
    - 60. 1931, June 15.L.A., Ca. Champion & Barber, Inc. (D.R.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 61. 1931, June 19.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 62. 1931, July 1.L.A., Ca. Standard, Pipe & Supply Co. (J.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 63. 1931, July 3.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 64. 1931, July 8.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 65. 1931, July 10.West Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Corrugated Culvert Co. (E.W.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 66. 1931, July 10.San Jose, Ca. Kimball-Krogh Pump Co. to W.F.S. frag., T.L.
    - 67. 1931, July 11.L.A., Ca. Wilson-Spear Co. (A.W.S.) to R.E.S., T.L.S.
    - 68. 1931, July 12.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 69. 1931, July 14.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 70. 1931, July 23.L.A., Ca. Champion & Barber, Inc. (F.C.*) to W.[F.]S. re: pipe line., T.L.S.
    - 71. 1931, July 23.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co. (W.H.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 72. 1931, Aug. 1.S.F., Ca. W.R. Ames Co. (S.V.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 73. 1931, Aug. 4.L.A., Ca. Champion & Barber, Inc. (F.C.*) to W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 74. 1931, Aug. 4.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 75. 1931, Aug. 8.Houston, Texas. R.B. McLaughlin to W.B. Martin., T.L.
    - 76. 1931, Aug. 10.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 77. 1931, Aug. 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. E.R. Muttersbach, Deputy Surveyor, Santa Cruz Co. to W.S.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 78. 1931, Aug. 19.L.A., Ca. American Pipe & Steel Corp. Ltd. (C.W.T.) to the Texas Co., T.L.
    - 79. 1931, Aug. 19.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 80. 1931, Aug. 20.Houston, Texas. R.B. McLaughlin to W.B. Martin, the Texas Co., tel.
    - 81. 1931, Aug. 21.L.A., Ca. W.B. Martin to R.B. McLaughlin., tel.
    - 82. 1931, Aug. 24.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 83. 1931, Aug. 26.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 84. 1931, Aug. 28.L.A., Ca. The Texas Co. (W.B.M.) to R.B. McLaughlin re: irrigation pipes., T.L.S.
    - 85. 1931, Aug. 31.Houston, Texas. R.B. McLaughlin to W.B. Martin., T.L.
    - 86. 1931, Sept. 5.Salinas, Ca. Salinas Valley Concrete Pipe Co. (R.F.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 87. 1931, Sept. 7.Kilgore, Texas. Jacob Wolters to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 88. 1931, Sept. 21.Salinas, Ca. Salinas Valley Concrete Pipe Co. (R.F.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 89. 1931, Sept. 25.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mrs. W.F.S. to American Pipe & Steel Corp., Ltd., T.L.
    - 90. 1931, Sept. 25.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Standard Supply Co., T.L.
    - 91. 1931, Sept. 29.L.A., Ca. American Pipe & Steel Corp., Ltd. (O.W.K.) to Mrs. C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 92. 1931, Sept. 29.S.F., Ca. National Supply Co. (G.H.C.) to R.F. Baumgarten., T.L.S.
    - 93. 1931, Oct. 15.S.F., Ca. Calif. Joint Stock Land Bank (W.W.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 94. 1931, Oct. 16.American Pipe & Steel Corp., Ltd. (O.W.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 95. 1931, Oct. 22.Sunnyvale, Ca. Calif. Concrete Products Co., Inc. (J.T.D.) to W.F.S. re: irrigation pipe line., T.L.S.
    - 96. 1931, Oct. 29.S.F., Ca. Western Pipe & Steel Co. (A.C.P.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 97. 1931, Oct. 31.S.F, Ca. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. (O.H.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 98. 1931, Nov. 24.Sacramento, Ca. Dept. of Public Works (H.C.) to E.D. Rodgers., T.L.S.
    - 99. 1931, Dec. 8.Stanford Univ., Ca. Theodore Hoover to Mr. Steele re: irrigation pipe., A.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1. 1932, Jan. 4.Berkeley, Ca. Federal Land Bank of Berkeley (F.R.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1932, Jan. 6.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co., Inc. (F.S.O.) to W.F.S. re: pea crop., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1932, Jan. 14.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co., Inc. (W.H.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1932, Jan. 16.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Bank of Savings & Loan. (B.L.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1932, Jan. 20.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1932, Jan. 20.N.P. Unknown to Montague Pipe & Steel Co., T.L.
    - 7. 1932, Jan. 20.N.P. Unknown to Salinas Valley Concrete Pipe Co., T.L.
    - 8. 1932, Jan. 20.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1932, Jan. 20.Stanford Univ., Ca. Hilda V. Tanner to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1932, Jan. 23.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1932, Jan. 23.N.P. Unknown [Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin] to Montague Pipe & Steel Co., T.L.
    - 12. 1932, Jan. 27.Watsonville, Ca. Sans & Hudson (A.W.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1932, Jan. 30.Redwood City, Ca. San Mateo Co. Title Co. (M.K.W.) to Santa Cruz Co. Title Co., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1932, Jan. 30.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1932, Feb. 5.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to F.W.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1932, Feb. 5.N.P. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to Montague Pipe & Steel Co., T.L.
    - 17. 1932, Feb. 24.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Bank of Savings & Loan (E.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1932, Feb. 29.S.F., Ca. Anglo-Calif. Trust Co. (L.S.) to Santa Cruz Bank of Savings & Loan., T.L.
    - 19. 1932, Mar. 7.S.F., Ca. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. (O.H.F.) to Santa Cruz Bank of Savings & Loan., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1932, Mar. 10.Santa Cruz Bank of Savings & Loan (E.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1932, Mar. 16.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1932, Mar. 16.N.P. [S.F., Ca.]. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin to Anglo-Calif. Trust Co., T.L.
    - 23. 1932, Mar. 18.S.F., Ca. Anglo-Calif. Trust Co. (L.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1932, April 14.S.F., Ca. Pacific Pipe Co. (E.I.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1932, April 15.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1932, April 21.S.F., Ca. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. (O.H.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1932, May 4.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to T.J. Horgan Co., T.L.
    - 28. [1932, May 4.][Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca.]. [W.F.S.] to [T.J. Horgan Co.]., A.L.
    - 29. 1932, May 23.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Bank of Savings & Loan. (E.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1932, May 24.Stanford Univ., Ca. Theodore J. Hoover to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1932, July 7.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co., Inc. (W.H.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1932, Sept. 22.Berkeley, Ca. Federal Land Bank of Berkeley (W.C.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1932, Sept. 24.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co., Inc. (W.H.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1932, Oct. 5.San a Cruz, Ca. Bank of America (W.C.*) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1932, Oct. 27.Same as # 34.
    - 36. 1932, Dec. 20.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (E.B.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1. 1933, Jan. 3.Santa Cruz, Ca. Rittenhouse & Snyder (B.B.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1933, Jan. 17.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley National Bank (L.H.L.) to Walter Carmean., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1933, Jan. 18.Santa Cruz, Ca. Bank of America (W.C.*) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1933, Mar. 15.S.F., Ca. Chapman & Co. (E.W.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1933, May 3.S.F., Ca. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. to T.J.Horgan Co., T.L.
    - 6. 1933, May 9.N.P. [S.F., Ca.]. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. to T.J. Horgan Co., T.L.
    - 7. 1933, May 22.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Unknown [W.F.S.] to Atkins., T.L.
    - 8. 1933, May 23.N.P. David Amins(?) to W.F.S. re: water right-of-way., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1933, June 26.N.P. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. to T.J. Horgan Co., Inc., T.L.
    - 10. 1933, July 31.S.F., Ca. Dept. of Agriculture (W.L.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1933, Aug. 1.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S. re: legal matters., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1933, Sept. 6.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin (R.S.L.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1933, Sept. 27.Oakland, Ca. Mother to Worden Wolters., A.L.S.
    - 14. 1933, Oct. 27.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co., Inc. (W.H.G.) to W.F.S. re: lease agreement., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1933, Nov. 2.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co., Inc. (W.H.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1933, Nov. 3.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1933, Nov. 4.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to T.J. Horgan Co., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1933, Nov. 7.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to T.J. Horgan Co., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1933, Nov. 9.N.P. T.J. Horgan Co., Inc. to Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell re: lease agreements., T.L.
    - 20. 1933, Nov. 12.Pescadero, Ca. Unknown to Treadwell re: lease agreement. frag., T.L.
    - 21. 1933, Nov. 15.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Unknown [W.F.S.] to Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell., T.L.
    - 22. 1933, Nov. 18.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Van Fleet & Laughlin (R.S.L.) to W.F.S. re: lease agreement., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1933, Nov. 23.Green Oaks, Pescadero, Ca. C.[B.S.] to General [Jacob F. Wolters]., T.L.
    - 24. 1933, Nov. 24.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co., Inc. (W.H.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1. 1934, Jan. 12.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1932, Feb. 1.S.F., Ca. Prudential Insurance Co. of America (O.O.O.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1934, Feb. 15.Watsonville, Ca. T.J. Horgan Co., Inc. (W.H.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1934, Mar. 14.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (W.C.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1934, Mar. 26.Berkeley, Ca. Same as # 4.
    - 6. 1934, April 19.Pescadero, Ca. Ray Tachiki to W.F. & I.C. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 7. 1934, April 19.S.F., Ca. Edward F. Treadwell to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1934, April 20.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell to Mary De Fremery Atkins, David Atkins and Flora E. Steele re: pipe line agreement., T.L.
    - 9. 1934, April 24.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1934, April 24.N.P. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1934, April 26.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1934, April 30.Houston, Texas. The Texas Co. (J.F.W.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1934, May 1.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell. (E.F.T.) to W.F.S. re: water agreements., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1934, May 4.S.F., Ca. Treadwell Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S. re: water pumping agreement., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1934, May 8.Santa Cruz, Ca. J.L. Johnston to Lee Ross re: estate of Chloe R. Steele., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1934, May 11.N.P. Bayer Fertilizer Service. (H.F.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1934, May 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. First Congregational Church (H. St. C.M.) to Mr. & Mrs. F.W.S. [W.F.S.], T.L.S.
    - 18. 1934, May 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Rittenhouse & Snyder to W.F.S. re: Steele vs. Horgan estate., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1934, May 24.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley National Farm Loan Assoc. (W.S.B.) to [W.]F.S., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1934, June 1.N.P. Ralph F. Baumgarten to Theo. J. Hoover re: water use., T.L.
    - 21. 1934, June 1.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz County Title Co. (H.O.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1934, June 13.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1934, June 18.Berkeley, Ca. Federal Land Bank of Berkeley, (C.H.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1934, July 3.Pescadero, Ca., Ralph F. Baumgarten to T.J. Hoover re: water use., T.L.
    - 25. 1934, July 11.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (C.H.A.) to Santa Cruz Title Co., T.L.
    - 26. 1934, July 13.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1934, July 25.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (C.H.A.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co., T.L.
    - 28. Same as # 27.
    - 29. 1934, July 30.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C.B.S. to David Atkins., A.L.S.
    - 30. 1934, Aug. 10.San Mateo, Ca. Levy Bros. (J.D.B.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1934, Aug. 10.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (C.H.A.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co., T.L.
    - 32. 1934, Aug. 27.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (C.H.A.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co., T.L.
    - 33. 1934, Sept. 12.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (E.B.S.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co., T.L.
    - 34. 1934, Sept. 29.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Bank of Savings & Loan (J.E.C.*) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1934, Oct. 1.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 36. 1934, Oct. 2.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (T.E.G.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co., T.L.
    - 37. 1934, Oct. 8.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 38. 1934, Oct. 17.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1934, Oct. 22.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (H.C.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1934, Oct. 29.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley National Farm Loan Assoc. (W.S.B.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co., A.L.S.
    - 41. 1934, Nov. 2.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1934, Nov. 20.N.P. Kirkbride, Wilson & Brooks to Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell re: agreement between W.F.S. & Flora E. Steele., T.L.
    - 43. 1934, Nov. 21.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to Charles N. Kirkbride re: agreement between W.F.S. & Flora E. Steele., T.L.
    - 44. 1934, Nov. 22.N.P. Kirkbride, Wilson & Brooks to Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell re: W.F.S. & Flora E. Steele agreement., T.L.
    - 45. 1934, Nov. 23.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1934, Nov. 24.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley to Santa Cruz County Title Co., T.L.
    - 47. 1934, Dec. 6.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 48. 1934, Dec. 6.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (J.C.S.) to Santa Cruz, County Title Co., T.L.
    - 49. Same as # 48.
    - 50. 1934, Dec. 8.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land Title Co. (H.O.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 51. 1934, Dec. 10.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 52. 1934, Dec. 11.S.F., Ca. R.E.S. to Will [W.F.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 53. 1934, Dec. 13.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz County Title Co. (H.O.H.) to Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley re: legal agreements., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1934, Dec. 18.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (W.F.M.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co., T.L.
    - 55. 1934, Dec. 21.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (W.F.M.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1. 1935, Jan. 2.S.F., Ca. Calif. Barrel Co., Ltd. to Unknown., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1935, Jan. 5.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (C.E.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1935, Jan. 23.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (W.F.M.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co., T.L.
    - 4. 1935, Feb. 1.Santa Cruz, Ca. Farmers Cooperative Exchange, Inc. to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1935, Feb. 21.Sames as #3.
    - 6. 1935, Mar 23.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Alec [Alex] Johnson, Farm Bureau Federation., T.L.
    - 7. 1935, Mar. 23.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (A.J.) to W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1935, Mar. 25.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mrs. W.F.S. to David Atkins., T.L.